Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IX: Audio Visual Materials, 1962-2009
  - Subseries 3: Moving Images, 1965-2000
    - UWP Performance on NBC-TV, film of the TV screen, silent, color (4 minutes), undated; 8mm movie film (Box 163, Item 2)
    - US Army Post Germany (2 minutes), undated; 3/4” Umatic (Box 163, Item 3)
    - “Viva la Gente Panama” (25 minutes: 885 feet), undated; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 163, Item 4)
    - “Which Way, America?” (20 minutes: 693 feet), undated; 16mm sound motion picture film (Box 163, Item 5)
    - Wild track bus interior & arrival in Tucson, EE80-16 (8 minutes: 288 feet), undated; 16 mm magnetic film (Box 163, Item 6)
    - WIM Video! (75 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 163, Item 7)
    - World in Motion Campaign spots (5 minutes), undated; 1/2” VHS (Box 163, Item 8)
- Series X: Memorabilia, 2009, undated
  This series is composed of costumes, buttons, and other artifacts that are significant to the Up with People organization.
  - 3 Costumes, undated (Box 164, Item 1)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 164, Item 2)
  - UWP Patch, undated (Box 164, Item 3)
  - Inflatable Globe, undated (Box 164, Item 4)
  - Celebrate Peace banner, undated (Box 164, Item 5)
  - Luggage tags, undated (Box 164, Item 6)
  - Deed of Gift Signing pen, 2009 (Box 165, Item 1)
  - DVD- Viva La Gente 79A, undated (Box 165, Item 2)
  - Piece of Berlin wall, undated (Box 165, Item 3)